？我们这代人 出生于战争时期
My generation… we were born into war.
巨兽袭击了我们的世界
Giant monsters attacked our world.
我们称之为 怪兽
We called 'em Kaiju.
它们来自虫洞
They came through the Breach.
通往另一次元的入口 位于太平洋的底部
A gateway to another dimension at the bottom of the Pacific Ocean.
派它们来的是虫洞另一端的外星种族
They were sent by an alien race on the other side…
名为 先驱
the Precursors.
我们予以回击
We fought back,
并造出了我们自己的怪物
building our own monsters…
机甲
Jaegars…
这些机器人 体型庞大
giant robots.
需要两名驾驶员才能操作
So big they needed two pilots to run 'em.
我父亲就是其中之一
My father was one of them.
他为了拯救世界 牺牲了自己
He sacrificed himself to help save the world.
而我 不是我父亲
I… am not my father.
自从我们赢得战争 并关闭虫洞
It's been ten years since we won the war…
已经过去了十年
and closed the Breach.
大部分地区已经重建
Most of the world's recovered.
但是一些沿海城市从未改变
But a few coastal cities never did.
整个世界仍在休养生息
And the world is still picking up the pieces.
可我们中的一些人更愿意住在废墟里
But some of us live better in a broken world.
待在断壁残垣的豪宅里
And squatting in half a mansion…
总比买那些海景公寓强
is better than paying for some crappy apartment.
在救援区 你得生财有道
Now, in the relief zones, you have to get creative.
会做交易
You have to hustle.
否则别人会吃掉你的早餐
Or somebody else might eat your breakfast.
还有你的饼干
And your cookies.
还有紧俏的辣椒酱
And your damn hot sauce.
在这里 我们赋予物品不同的价值
You know, out here, we place a different value on things.
然而「环太平洋联合军防部队」通常不这么认为
The Pan Pacific Defense Corps usually looks the other way…
只要你别去那些不该去的地方
as long as you don't go poking around where you don't belong.
比如退役机甲的废料场
Say, like a decommissioned Jaeger scrapyard.
（加利福尼亚 圣塔莫尼卡）
俗话说 富贵险中求
Big risks mean big reward,
盗取机甲技术是最赚钱的
and nothing pays more than stolen Jaeger tech.
在这里 很多疯子都想组装自己的机甲
Plenty of nutcases out here trying to slap together their own Jaegers.
可他们得有零件才行
But they need the parts to do it.
如果你能偷到别人偷不到的东西
So, if you can steal what no one else can steal…
你就能过上国王般的生活
you can live like a king.
你确定这里有吗
Are you sure it's in here?
报废前 动力核心都会被拆掉
Power cores are stripped before they get decommissioned.
不过偶尔会忘掉三级等离子电容器
But sometimes they miss the tertiary plasma capacitors.
可能性很大 你看这个 你还有电
And that's a big score. This one's still holding a charge.
最好是这样
You better hope so.
那好吧
Okay.
冷静别激动
Let's just calm down. Let's not get excited.
我只是以防万一
I'm just playing the odds here.
你在华雷斯骗了布雷塔 在香港又把老周耍了
You cheated Barada in Juarez, skipped out on Chau in Hong Kong.
- 那是误会 - 还在我的后院
- Now, that was a misunderstanding. - And stole from me…
偷我的东西
in my own backyard.
可现在我是为你而偷 低头不见抬头见的
Now I'm stealing for you. Circle of life.
- 交个朋友怎么样 - 你先把东西给我
- We good? - You deliver…
行
and yeah…
成交
we're good.
好
Okay.
- 我们发财去 - 走
- Let's get rich. - Let's.
目标已锁定
Target lock.
那东西在哪
Where is it?
目标已锁定
Target lock.
老兄 出了点状况
Hey, man, uh, just a little situation.
这玩意儿说它在那儿 它就应该在那
It says it's here. It's supposed to be right there,
但你也看到这种状况了 我来看看是怎么回事
but you know what, let me just figure this out.
目标已锁定
Target lock.
来个人给我把他干掉
Somebody please kill this guy for me.
目标在移动
Target moving.
不不不 它在这儿 你等等 等等
No, no, no. It's here. You wait, wait.
这里还有别人
Someone else is in here.
电容器让他拿走了 我们追 快点
Someone else has the capacitor. Now, let's go. Come on.
杰克
Jake! Jake!
等一等
Hey, wait!
你这个混蛋
Son of a…
快快快快
Go, go, go!
分头追
Split up.
快点
Go!
别跑 杰克
Come on! Jake!
老大 到这边来
Hey, boss, he went over here!
快快快
Go, go, go!
我看见他了
I see him. I see him.
这边
This way.
杰克
Jake, Jake, Jake.
你可真滑头啊
Nice try.
对
Yeah.
杰克
Jake!
朋友嘛
We're good.
杰克
Jake!
（警告 请勿靠近此门）
杰克 你这个混蛋
Jake, you son of a…
目标已锁定
Target lock.
把东西交出来
Hey! Get back here with that!
不不不
No, no!
目标正在移动
Target moving.
（帮助打赢这场仗 怪兽袭击加剧）
（怪兽之战结束）
（邵氏酝酿技术收购）
（第六代机甲）
- 你多大了 - 打败你绰绰有余
- How old are you? - Old enough to kick your ass.
等一下 别动
Let's take a second. Back up. Back up.
- 那是你造的吗 - 你以为呢
- You build this thing yourself? - What do you think?
我以为可以卖掉你的小玩具 赚一大笔钱
I think I can sell your little toy for a whole lot of money.
拳击手可不是玩具 它是非卖品
Scrapper's not a toy and she's not for sale.
谁手里拿着棍子谁说了算 你给我听着
The man holding the pipe says she is. So listen up…
- 是你把他们领来的 - 怎么可能
- You led them here? - That's impossible.
搞什么鬼 老兄
Ah, what the hell, man?
快点快点
Come on, come on, come on.
行了
Yes.
启动了
It works!
好的
Okay.
喂喂喂
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
出去
Get out…
你要干什么
What are you doing?
- 不不不 住手 - 它在哪儿
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop! - Where is it?
别碰那个
Hey! Don't touch that. Hey.
你要干什么
What are you doing?!
- 另一个在哪 - 住手 另一个什么
- Where's the other one? - Stop! The other what?
另一个驾驶位 机甲需要两名驾驶员
The other cradle. A Jaeger needs two pilots.
拳击手是小机甲 所以一个神经元就能操控
Scrapper is small enough to run on a single neural lobe.
好吧 那你出去 我来驾驶
All right, then you get out, you let me pilot.
快出去
Get out!
去死吧你
Screw that.
我说了 它不是玩具
Told you she's not a toy.
你会害死我们的 我能让我们逃出去
You're gonna get us killed. I can get us out of here.
我已经让我们逃出来了
I just got us out.
天那
Oh, my God.
（接近警戒目标 警告）
那是「冬日阿贾克斯」
That's November Ajax.
未经注册的机甲驾驶员
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
我们是环太平洋联合军防部队
this is the Pan Pacific Defense Corps.
关闭动力 并从驾驶舱里出来
Power down and exit your Conn-Pod.
不不不 别投降
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't-don't-don't give up.
你太缺乏斗志了
You give up way too easy.
他们也是这么认为的
That's what they think.
站住
Stop!
你违反的时候禁止令第14条 驾驶未经注册的机甲
You are in violation of Code Ten, Section 14. Operation of an unregistered Jaeger.
- 抓好 - 我抓着好着呢
- Hang on. - I am hanging on!
抓紧点儿
Hang tighter.
还跑
Seriously?
站住
Stop.
看见没有 我甩掉了冬日阿贾克斯
See? I just out-piloted November Ajax.
- 不 你没有 - 我有
- No, you didn't. - Did…
你没有
Didn't.
好吧 那你有什么办法 我是不会出去的
Okay. What do you got? And I'm not getting out.
- 能拿掉一个离子电池吗 - 不能
- One of those ion cells redundant? - No!
现在必须能
They are now.
- 可我们需要它 - 爬到阿贾克斯头上去
- But we need them. - Get up to Ajax's head.
- 什么 - 上啊
- What? - Go!
关闭动力
Power down.
动力不足警报 12%
Low power warning. 12%.
我说了 我们需要它
I told you we needed that!
可我们不是成功了吗
It worked, didn't it?
警告 11%
11%.
阿贾克斯重启系统要多久
How long before Ajax can reboot his systems?
怎么这么久
About that long.
关闭动力
Power down.
这是最后一次警告
This is your final warning.
好了 跟我走
All right, let's go.
看看你对我的机甲都做了什么
Look what you did to my Jaeger…
你这个大傻个
you jerk!
- 你应该让我来驾驶的 - 怎么怪起我来了
- Should have let me pilot. - Oh, like this is my fault.
- 你暴露了我的指挥中心 - 你的指挥中心吗
- You compromised my command center. - Your command center?
- 没错 我的指挥中心 - 等等 抱歉
- Yes. My command center. - Wait. Sorry, sorry.
- 我没听清 你的指挥中心 - 没错
- I didn't hear that. Your command center? - Yes!
鬼知道你是从哪冒出来的 对我指指点点
And you had no place to come in and try to tell me what to do.
- 我想怎样就怎样 - 所以结果又怎样呢
- I go wherever I want. - 'Cause it really worked out well, right?
- 这世界不一样了 - 看看我们的下场
- It's a different world. - Look where we're at.
你的上嘴皮和下嘴皮需要碰面 交个朋友
Your top lip and your bottom lip, they need to meet and become friends.
你厉害 你说的真棒
Smart. That's a good one.
它们需要闭上 好吗
Need to close up, all right? Shut up.
- 闭嘴 - 没问题
- Shut up. - Yeah, I can.
- 谈话到此结束 - 很好
- Conversation done. - Good.
捡破烂的丫头
Junkyard baby.
你造它干什么
Why did you build it?
你不是让我把嘴闭上吗
What happened to the shutting up?
你又不卖它 那你造它干什么
You said you wasn't gonna sell it, so what the hell was you gonna do?
还不如抢银行
Rob a bank or something?
我找它 是因为它们迟早会回来
I built her because one day they're gonna come back.
那些怪兽
The Kaiju.
到时候我就不用再傻傻的等着
And when they do, I'm not gonna be stuck waiting…
别人来救我的命
for someone else to come save my ass.
不会像以前那样
Not like before.
你 出来
You. Let's go.
（犯罪记录）
我不想再谈这事儿 太荒唐了
I don't really want to talk about it. It's ridiculous. That's just, like, my right or…
（环太平洋联合军方部队）
你好 杰克
Hello, Jake.
我们又在这儿见面了
Here we are again.
运气不好而已 我能应付
It's just a stretch of bad luck. I'll figure it out.
父亲过去常说
Father used to say…
运气掌握在自己手中
we make our own luck.
对 老爸说过很多
Yeah, well, Dad said a lot of things.
你是在非法机甲里被当场抓获的
You were arrested in a rogue Jaeger.
等一下 那可不是我的机甲我
Hold on a second. That wasn't my Jaeger.
- 有个小不点 大概这么高 - 你有前科
- There's this little kid, she's about this tall… - You have priors.
这是非常严重的
This is serious.
对 所以才需要我的老姐
Okay. That's why I need my big sis…
把我从这个地方弄出去
to help me get the hell out of here.
这是最后一次
Just one last time.
我们不可能就这么让你走出去
They're not going to let you just walk.
- 也许有其他的办法 - 没问题
- But there might be another way. - Okay.
对了 这才是我想听的
See, that's what I want to hear.
我就是想谈这个 别的办法
That's what I'm here to talk about, the other way.
跟我说吧 需要我做什么
Lay it on me. What do I got to do?
重新入伍 完成你以前的训练
Reenlist and finish what you started.
我不干
I'm not doing that.
你看 我太老了 不适合再当学员了
I'm… look, I'm-I'm too old to be a cadet.
我不是让你当学员
I don't want you to be a cadet.
而是让你去训练他们
I want you to help train them.
训练谁 练什么
Train who? Train what?
我可不想教那些熊孩子
I'm not training no damn kids.
运输机已经准备好了
The transport is standing by…
要送你们去莫玉兰基地了
to bring both of you to Moyulan.
我们是谁
Both of us?
你和你的新学员
You and your new recruit.
麻子
Mako.
她居然用视频就把我打发了
I can't believe she just hologrammed me.
（环太平洋联合军防部队猎人学院）
（中国 莫玉兰基地）
是 我没得选择
Yeah, look, I didn't have a choice.
我知道 我明白
I know, I get it,
可是为什么我也要来
but why me?
他们为什么要我参加这个项目
Why do they want me for the program?
你自己找了个机甲 还能驾驶它
You built and piloted your own Jaeger.
他们就喜欢你这样的
These people like that kind of stuff.
好吧 那为什么我只是个学员
Okay, so then why am I just a cadet…
而你却是战士
and you get to be a ranger?
勇士欧米茄
Valor Omega.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
那是勇士欧米茄
That, that is Valor Omega.
拳击手
Scrapper.
我不是在做梦吧
You got to be kidding me.
他们跟我说你回来了 我还不相信
I didn't believe it when they told me you were inbound.
最近怎么样 奈特
How you doing, Nate?
叫我兰伯特战士
It's Ranger Lambert.
你是在嘲笑我吗
Are you having a laugh?
这里是军事基地
Well, this is a military base.
你记得这儿的规矩吧
You remember how that works,
潘特考斯特战士
Ranger Pentecost.
你就是阿玛拉·纳马尼吧
You must be Amara Namani.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
战士 长官
Ranger, sir.
我带你去办理报到手续
Well, let's get you squared away.
对了 在这里你可别偷东西
Oh, and, uh, try not to steal anything while you're here.
那家伙刚才叫你潘特考斯特
Did that haircut just call you Pentecost?
是那个了不起的斯塔克·潘特考斯特
As in badass Stacker Pentecost?
探戈狼机甲的驾驶员
Pilot of Coyote Tango,
拯救全世界的大英雄吗
hero of basically the whole world?
就是个名字而已
It's just a name.
对 如雷贯耳
Yeah, a really cool name.
模拟训练 六点钟开始
Sim training starts at 0600.
如果迟到 就算旷课一天
You're late, you miss the day.
如果掉队 马上送你上飞机
You fall behind, you'll be on the next transport…
哪儿来的回哪儿去
back to wherever they found you.
那是 救赎者泰坦
That's Titan Redeemer.
还有凤凰游击士
And Bracer Phoenix.
它需要三个人来驾驶
She's a three-man rig.
军刀雅典娜
Saber Athena.
我爱死军刀雅典娜了
I love Saber Athena.
它是所有机甲里最快的 你知道吗
She's the fastest Jaeger in the fleet. Did you know that?
警告 请远离升降台
Warning: stand clear of lift.
对了 哪个是你的
Okay, so which one's yours?
流浪者
Gipsy.
你驾驶复仇流浪者吗
You pilot Gipsy Avenger?
以前是
He used to…
后来他的搭档被私营公司高薪挖走了
until his copilot got a better offer in the private sector.
我是朱尔斯·雷耶斯 机甲工程师
Jules Reyes, J-Tech.
我是阿玛拉 学员
Amara, cadet.
我是杰克 战士 显而易见
Jake. Ranger, apparently.
久仰大名 潘特考斯特
Heard a lot about you, Pentecost.
是吗
Yeah?
要知道 你还是那个纪录的保持者
You know you still hold the record?
什么记录
What record?
闭嘴
Shut up.
他们是怎么把你引诱回来的
So how did they lure you back?
我觉得 肯定不是用钱
I mean, it couldn't have been the pay, so…
这可说来话长
Oh, yeah, it's a long story, but if you,
如果你想知道 我们可以约一下
if you want to talk about it, we can meet up…
她没空
She's busy.
战士
Ranger.
向前看 潘特考斯特
Eyes front, Pentecost.
拜托 蕾娜塔 不要打脸好不好
Oh! Come on, Renata, not the face!
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, man.
我再押两张淋浴券
And raise you two shower chits.
弃牌吧 伊利亚
Fold, Ilya.
你再不洗澡就臭死了 兄弟
You need all the showers you can get, man.
那是麝香味儿
I have a musk!
你们闻到的是麝香味
What you smell is musk.
战士来了
Ranger on deck!
音频系统停止使用
Audio system deactivated.
学员们 这是阿玛拉·纳马尼
Cadets. This is Amara Namani.
明天早上她也参加你们的模拟训练
She'll be joining you in sim training bright and early.
这是潘特考斯特战士
And this is Ranger Pentecost.
他会帮我训练你们
He will be helping me instruct you…
直到我找到新的搭档代替波克战士
until I can find a new copilot to replace Ranger Burke.
你有什么想补充的
Anything you'd like to add?
说了你也不爱听
Nothing you want to hear.
玛丽科娃
Malikova,
纳马尼交给你了 帮她准备明天的训练
get Namani squared away and prepped for training.
是 长官
Yes, sir!
解散
As you were.
潘特考斯特
Pentecost.
竟然是潘特考斯特要来训练我们
We're gonna be trained by a Pentecost!
那又怎么样
So?
他可不像牺牲自己堵住虫洞的那位
Not like he was the one who died helping close the Breach.
他甚至都没上过战场
He's never even been in combat.
蕾娜塔 来两局
Renata, let's go for round two.
伊利亚 看见没
Yo, Ilya, you see this? Ah!
那我应该去哪儿
So, where should I…
听说你自己造了个小机甲
Heard you built your own little Jaeger.
是的 它叫拳击手
Yeah, actually. Uh, Scrapper.
而且是可以单人驾驶的机甲
I operated her, too, with this solo bay…
如果你想组装垃圾 就去当机械工
You want to put junk together, be a mechanic.
莫玉兰是训练驾驶员的地方
Moyulan is for pilots.
来吧 我领你去
Hey, come on. I got ya.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是
Um…
津海 欧阳津海
Jinhai. Ou-yang Jinhai.
你跟维柯算是认识了
So, you and Vik already buddies, huh?
维柯
Vik?
是维多利亚的简称
It's short for Viktoriya.
不过你应该不想那么叫她
But you don't want to call her that.
她是怎么回事
Yeah, what's her problem?
她考了三次才通过入学测试
Took her three shots to pass the entrance test.
没错 所以她认为你能来这里是走了捷径
Don't think she likes how you landed here.
这能怪我吗
Yeah, well, it's not my fault.
我又不是走后门进来的
Recruiters never come around back home.
会说俄语吗
Hey, know any Russian?
不会
No.
那我教你几句 好让她消消气
I'll teach you some. Calms her down.
走 我带你熟悉一下这儿的环境
Come on. Let's get you squared away.
脑半球失去协调 警告
Hemispheres out of alignment. Warning.
我得重新进行对接
We need to reconnect!
我知道 我在努力
I know! I'm trying!
磁悬浮系统已经关闭
MAGLEV deactivated.
我真的适应不了
I just can't get this.
糟糕透了
That sucked.
（阿玛拉·纳马尼失败 苏雷什·库拉纳失败）
听说你能把冬日阿贾克斯耍的团团转
You know, when I heard you gave November Ajax a run for his money,
我还以为出了个天才
I thought we might have something here.
现在我有些怀疑了
Now I'm not so sure.
戴这么个破东西怎么对接
How am I supposed to drift in this thing?
一股脚臭味儿
It smells like feet.
我不想听你找借口 学员
I didn't ask for your excuses, Cadet.
你让她对付的怪兽
You putting her up against Kaiju…
几乎能杀死久经沙场的驾驶员
that almost killed veteran pilots…
这不合常理
doesn't make any sense.
也许除了她 还有人也不适合留在这
Well, maybe she's not the only one that doesn't belong here.
奈特 我知道你看我不顺眼
Wow. See, Nate, I know you have a problem with me.
但看在她还是个孩子的份上
But come on. She's just a kid.
我们曾经也是 这就是关键
So were we. That's the point.
在年轻时 强化巩固对接形成的默契
You make stronger connections when you're young.
能够造就更好的对接驾驶员
And that kind of bond makes for a better drift pilot.
是 我也记得这些 谢谢
Yeah. I remember the pitch.Thanks…
良一 蕾娜塔 你们上
Ryoichi, Renata, you're up.
让我们的新人看看该怎么做
Show our new recruit how it's done.
你穿的那是什么啊
What the hell are you wearing?
朱尔斯喜欢
Jules loves it.
她说这里终于来了个型男 太好了
Yeah, she told me it's nice to finally have someone with style around here.
不能怪人家姑娘 我本来就性感
Can't blame the girl. I'm sexy…
好吧
Yeah.
要喝吗
Want a drink?
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
冰淇淋在上面
Ice cream's up top.
了解我 太了解我了
Yes. Yes.
所以你这次又回来
So, one more time around, huh?
是想证明你老爸说错了吗
Prove your old man wrong?
不 我只是回来看看
Nah, I just came back to see…
你的下巴整得怎么样
if your chin implant ever settled in.
我觉得整的相当的不错
Well, I think it's settled in quite nicely.
确实 看着挺威严的
Yeah. It's very commanding.
孩子们一定很喜欢
Kids must love it.
杰克 这些孩子们 他们仰慕我们
Jake, these kids, they look up to us.
得让他们看看 我们能够通力合作
We got to show them that we can work together.
老兄 战争十年前就结束了
Well, the war ended ten years ago, man.
你只要随它去 就像
You just need to let that go. Just… woosah.
你必须了解敌人的
Y-You have to understand your enemy's ob…
你必须
You have…
我很抱歉 伙计
Sorry, mate.
你只有真正了解敌人的目的
You have to understand your enemy's objective…
才知道是否打败了他
to know you've defeated 'em.
我们还不了解
We still don't.
不 关于这一点我可以告诉你
No. I can help you out with that.
我觉得它们派怪兽来 无非是想
See, I'm thinking it has something to do with them…
让人类彻底灭绝
sending giant monsters to kick the crap out of us.
不 先驱如果想让我们从地球上消失
No, no, no. The Precursors wouldn't send Kaiju to flatten a few cities…
不会只让怪兽破坏几座城市
if they were trying to wipe us all out.
听着 奈特 我对你没有成见
All right, look, Nate, I don't have a problem with you, man.
可我必须作出选择
But I had to make a choice.
在你帅气的脸蛋和监狱之间
It was between your pretty face and prison.
我选择了你帅气的脸蛋
I chose your pretty face.
我太感动了
Oh, well, I'm touched.
你到底还要加多少配料
And how many damn toppings do you need?
别管我的配料了 兄弟
Leave my toppings be, man.
别扫了我加配料的兴致
Don't mess with my damn toppings.
话说回来 那些学员还有多久
So the cadets got, like, what,
还有几个月就毕业了吗
couple of months before they graduate?
六个月
Six.
那好 我看这样吧
Okay. I'll tell you what.
每次你想对他们发号施令的时候
Every time you want to say something soldiery to 'em,
我都点头 或者说 没错 按他说的做
I'll just nod, or like, "Yep, what he said."
然后 不知不觉的
And then, before you know it,
他们就成为驾驶员了
they get to be pilots.
而且我也能回到我原有的生活了
And I get to get back to my life.
好极了
Great.
成交
Boom.
没准你能提前回家
It may happen sooner than you think.
什么情况
How so?
明天有场大型展示会
Big dog and pony show tomorrow.
邵和她的团队要来展示
Shao and her team are presenting…
他们新研发的自动驾驶系统
this new drone program they have.
也许以后我们就都失业了
Could make us all obsolete.
听着像是我的绝地重生之牌呢
Sounds like my "get out of jail free" card.
你可以对想要的一切表现的无所谓
You know, you can front all you want,
但你我都知道
but you and I both know…
你本来可以很伟大的
you could've been great.
邵小姐 我是权将军
幸会
抱歉 邵小姐是从来不握手的
Sorry. She doesn't do the whole hand shaking thing.
我是邵氏工业研发部的主管
Dr. Newton Geiszler, head of research…
纽特·葛斯乐博士
and development for Shao Industries.
这手握得 握得很有力啊
That's a nice firm, firm grip you got there, uh…
握得够紧
谢谢您的招待
我和兰伯特战士会马上帮您安排
你看起来精神多了
That's a much better look on you.
比穿监狱的囚服强一点
Guess it's better than prison stripes.
没强多少
Barely.
抱歉 就是他吗
I…I'm sorry, is this him?
一定是他 对吧 你就是斯塔克的孩子吧
It-It's got to be him, right? You're Stacker's kid.
我叫纽特 是你父亲的铁杆粉丝
Hey, uh, I'm Newt. I was, uh, I was a big fan of your father's.
他还是一个超级演说家
Amazing speech writer, by the way.
你听过他在阻止世界毁灭后的那次演讲吗
Did you ever hear his one where he canceled the apocalypse?
纽特
Newton.
赫尔曼
Hermann.
我一直希望你会跟着来
I was hoping you'd be tagging along.
我正在开展一项实验 需要你帮忙
I could use your help on an experiment I'm working on.
只要片刻工夫就好
Now, this will only take a moment.
我知道你特别忙
I know how busy you are.
是啊
Yeah.
我不想勉强你 可是
Don't want to impose, but, uh…
少来 你可勉强不了我
Aw, come on, you can't impose on me.
我们谁也不知道谁呀 对吧
I mean, we've been inside each other's heads, right?
我们拯救了世界
We've saved the world.
和怪兽成功对接了
We've drifted with a Kaiju!
要不是我们得到了怪兽大脑中的情报
You know, if we hadn't yanked that intel out of that Kaiju's brain,
罗利就不可能把虫洞关上
Raleigh would've never been able to close the Breach.
那可是靠你 靠我
Now, that was you and that was me.
严格来说主要是靠我 可
Technically more me,
咱们能快点吗 或者
but any chance we could make this quick or…
部署计划
Um, deployment.
机甲的
Of Jaegers.
部署它们投入战斗 需要花的时间实在是太长了
Deploying them into battle, it takes, takes too much time.
在那之前
The amount of damage…
城市就已经被怪兽毁了
a Kaiju can inflict before they've ev…
在这儿 我已经有办法了
Ah, here. I think I've found a solution.
赫尔曼 你知道 我没法读你的
Hermann, you know I can never read your, uh…
火箭推进器吗
Uh, rocket thrusters, huh?
了解 不行 不行
Yeah. No. No.
这世上没有人燃料能达到这个速率
No. There's no fuel in the world with that kind of boost-to-mass ratio.
这个世界没有
From this world.
那现在呢
No.
那是怪兽的血液吗
I…Is that Kaiju blood?
正是
Exactly.
我发现怪兽的血液在和稀有元素
I've discovered Kaiju blood is highly reactive…
结合时会发生剧烈的反应
when it's combined with rare earth elements…
铈元素 镧元素 钆元素
cerium, lanthanum, gadolinium.
我懂了 朋友 好吧
I realize that, pal. Okay.
你别举着它到处闲逛 会炸飞自己的
Y-You can't be fooling around with this stuff. You're gonna blow yourself up. Uh…
这世上最了解怪兽形态的只有你
Now, no one knows more about Kaiju morphology than you.
如果你能看上一眼
And if you could just take a look, please.
不 赫尔曼 我要阻止你
No, Hermann, I gotta stop you.
听着 这些都不重要
Look, none of this matters.
一旦我老板的无人机甲获得批准
Once my boss' drones are approved,
部署时间就不是问题了
deployment time, that's gonna be a non-issue.
一年之内
Within a year, buddy,
无人机甲会遍布各地
we're gonna have drones everywhere.
那你不帮我了
So you won't help me?
不如去我家边吃边谈吧
Look, why don't we talk about it over dinner at my place?
好吗 你还可以见见艾力丝
Okay? You can finally meet Alice.
我不需要一顿热乎乎的饭菜
I don't need a hot meal, Newton.
我需要的是针对这个问题的解决方案
What I need is a solution to a very specific problem.
是找我的 朋友 抱歉
Ah, that's me, bud. I'm sorry.
老板在召唤我了 很高兴见到你
Duty calls. It's been nice catching up.
纽特
Newton.
我还在 做噩梦 梦见和怪兽
I still get nightmares about what we saw…
对接时看到的
when we drifted with that…
那些恶心的画面
disgusting Kaiju brain.
是吗
Yeah.
可是
But…
一闪就没了 对吗
it was a hell of a rush, wasn't it?
葛斯乐博士 我们该走了
好 好
你和哥特里布博士的关系不一般 是吗
在打仗那会儿
是 我们以前
说英语
你说中文的时候听起来像个白痴
我知道 我的中文很糟糕
I…I know, I'm terrible.
是 以前我们在一个实验室工作
Uh, yes, we shared a lab together.
你和哥特里布博士刚才在聊什么
他有个疯狂的想法
Oh, some crazy idea he had about…
想在机甲上装个推进器
thruster pods on a, on a Jaeger.
在得到森麻子秘书长峰会上的举荐之前
我绝不允许有任何闪失
现在投票结果还没出来
不要再和他有任何联系
其实 这家伙是完全无害的
Oh. Well, the man's completely harmless. Uh…
别让我怀疑你的忠诚
好的
Okay.
好的 你能再说一遍吗
Could you say that again,
这次请放慢80%的速度
and this time about 80% slower?
我说 别让我怀疑你的忠诚
I said don't make me question your loyalty.
听懂了吗
Understand?
你在怀疑什么
Ay. What's to question?
你看 我几乎没跟他说过话
I… look, I barely talk to the guy anyway.
那就好
回去好好练练你的中文
我不喜欢重复我自己
无论是用哪种语言
我的无人机甲是机甲进化的下一步
My drones are the next step in Jaeger evolution.
我设计的这个系统
The system I designed processes commands…
通过量子数据内核处理指令
through a quantum data core.
这意味着一名驾驶员
This means that a single pilot…
通过远程对接 在世界任何地方都可以操作无人机甲
can operate the drone remotely from anywhere in the world.
只要基于森秘书最终报告的部署
As soon as the council approves deployment,
获得委员会的批准
based on Secretary General Mori's final report,
那些寻找 训练和对接驾驶员的艰难日子
the days of struggling to find and train drift compatible pilots…
就会成为历史了
will be a thing of the past.
你以为坐办公室的会比我们厉害吗
And you think a bunch of desk jockeys are better than us?
我们不是来砸人饭碗的
We are not here to shut you down.
现在至关重要的是我们项目的合作
Cooperation between our programs has never been more vital.
如果还有问题的话
If there are any questions.
我有很多问题
Yeah, I got a question right over here!
我们是驾驶员 不是坐办公室的
We are pilots, not a bunch of office workers!
都不要喊了 有话好好说嘛
And now we're shouting. There's no need to shout.
我觉得那个挺厉害的
Well, that was slick.
所以这还有多久才关门大吉
So, how long until all this is shut down…
好让我回家
so I can go home?
我不信任科技 至少现在还不信
I don't trust the tech. Not yet, at least.
我倒觉得挺好的
Well, it looks pretty good to me.
黑客能入侵或者干扰远程系统
Remote systems can be hacked or compromised.
你手上有关键的一票
No, you've got the key vote, right?
那不就得了 决定权在你那儿
So there you go. It's your decision.
我也希望我可以直接投赞成票
I wish I could just go ahead and approve them.
委员会里几乎一半的人都支持丽雯
Nearly half the council is backing Liwen.
他们不会喜欢我的决定
They aren't going to like my decision.
谁在乎他们喜不喜欢
Who cares what they like and what they don't like?
我跟你说吧 我站在你这边
I'll tell you what, I'm gonna go with you.
精神上支持你
For moral support.
另外 我想离开这里
Plus, I want to get out of this place.
我很高兴你说出来了
I'm glad you offered,
因为我已经请求让复仇流浪者
because I already requested Gipsy Avenger…
在委员会峰会上做荣誉护卫
as honor guard at the Council Summit.
你知道 复仇流浪者是奈特的
Look, you know Gipsy's Nate's ride.
他的搭档投靠丽雯了
His copilot works for Liwen now.
他需要一个新搭档
He needs a new one.
一个据你了解可对接的人
One that you already know is drift compatible.
好吧
All right.
我答应你 我得支持你的工作
I'll do it. I got your back.
不过你跟奈特说的时候 我也要在场
But I want to be there when you tell Nate,
因为我想看看他有什么反应
'cause I just want to see his face. He's gonna be so pissed.
他会站在那 说
He's just gonna stand there like,
机甲不适合你 杰克
"Yeah, I don't think you belong in a Jaeger, Jake.
从我的机甲里滚出去
Get out of my Jaeger.
我很帅 很性感
I'm handsome and sexy."
他确实很帅 很性感
He is handsome. He is sexy.
谢谢你 杰克
Thank you, Jake.
（澳大利亚 悉尼）
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我们用一个阳光明媚的日子 迎来了新的周末
Lots of sunshine today to kick off our weekend. The city…
大家下午好 我是彼得·欧文顿
Good afternoon, everyone. Peter Overton…
在悉尼的第九点播室 为您播送新闻
broadcasting from the Nine Studios in Sydney with the latest…
据警方透露
So far, police say…
目前已经有49名警务人员在冲突中受伤
at least 49 officers injured.
抗议者头戴黑色面具 投掷瓶子和石块
Kaiju worshippers in black masks throwing bottles and rocks.
军防部队穿戴防暴装备
PPDC security in riot gear…
严阵以待
are attempting to regain control…
复仇流浪者 我是权将军
Gipsy Avenger, this is Marshal Quan.
你只要威风凛凛的站在那就行了
All you have to do is stand there and look pretty.
精神集中点 尽量别摔倒
Stay focused, try not to fall over.
收到 长官
Roger that, sir.
准备投放
Go for drop.
三 二 一 投放
In three, two, one. Drop!
杰克
Jake!
同步对接出现紊乱
Drift alignment unstable.
没事 我找回感觉了
Relax. It's coming back to me.
真的吗
You sure?
离子电池已经激活
Ion cells activated.
我们是彼此相通的 记得吗
And hey… We're in each other's heads, remember?
如果你不对朱尔斯想入非非 我会感激不尽
So I'd appreciate it if you'd stop thinking about Jules.
你没戏
Not gonna happen.
你不是也在想着要干掉我
How about you stop thinking about kicking my ass?
那也没戏
Not gonna happen either.
这日子怎么熬啊
Gonna be a long day.
报告将军 半球已校准
神经元连接较弱 但是在保持
有外部通讯请求接入
Incoming transport.
（接触外部通讯 秘书长 森麻子）
（无人机甲可行性报告）
警告
Warning.
流浪者呼叫指挥中心 看到了吗
Gipsy to Command. You reading this?
流浪者 这里是指挥中心
Gipsy, this is Command.
突然出现不明机甲
Be advised, we have a rogue Jaeger.
未经注册机甲
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
马上关闭电源 并离开你的驾驶舱
power down and exit your Conn-Pod immediately.
重复一遍 马上关闭电源 并离开驾驶舱
I repeat: power down and exit your Conn-Pods now.
注意导弹
Missiles fired!
快 快
- 动力不足警报 - 我们在失去动力
- Low power. Warning. - We're losing power!
（动力特征）
杰克 不明机甲的动力参数和你的一样
Jake! That Jaeger's power reading is the same…
它在干扰我们的通讯
It's jamming our comms!
奈特
Nate!
动力恢复了
Power's up!
该死
Oh, shit.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
听我指挥
Follow my lead!
麻子中弹了
Mako's hit!
她在下坠 我们得救她
She's going down! We've gotta move!
启动引力弹弓
Activating gravity sling!
求救
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
我是MMC052 我们中弹了 正在下坠
This is Mike, Mike, Charlie, zero, five, two! We have been hit and we are going down!
发送
Sending.
麻子
Mako!
杰克 回来
Jake! Wait!
同步对接失败
Drift alignment failing.
拜托 莎拉
Come on, Sarah!
- 想想办法 - 同步对接失败
- Do something… - Drift alignment failing.
你这个破脑子是不是傻掉了
You stupid brain thing!
我不太擅长劝人
So, I'm not really good at emotional stuff,
不过
but…
你姐姐的事 我很遗憾
I really am sorry about your sister.
或者是同父异母什么的
Half sister?
她父母在恶魔女巫袭击时遇难了
Yeah, her family died during the Onibaba attack.
我父亲收养了她
My dad took her in.
她是我的姐姐
And she was my sister.
是我的家人
My family.
你怎么没穿制服
Why are you out of uniform?
悉尼那件事之后 我脑子里很乱
Just had a lot on my mind after Sydney.
所以想穿得舒服些
Guess I just wanted to be comfortable.
你可别让兰伯特战士看见你穿这个
Well, don't let Ranger Lambert see you in that.
他搞不好会掏出武器打你
He might take the stick out of his butt and beat you with it.
我觉得我还挺安全 它塞得紧紧的
I think I'm safe. It's wedged in there pretty tight.
他们还在使用莎拉
So they're still using Sarah.
对 不知道为什么 就是对接不上
Yeah. And I can't drift with her for some reason.
其他学员已经训练了好几年 而我
All the other cadets have been training for years and I just…
我讨厌自己是个小孩子
I hate feeling like the slow kid.
这事不能勉强
You gotta relax.
我帮你跟她进行对接
Or you're just grinding gears. I'll help you out.
好的 教练
Got it, coach.
别叫我教练
Don't call me coach.
好的 先生
All right, sensei.
精神集中
Concentrate.
最好能一次成功
You have to make a good connection.
抱怨只会导致失败
You can't do that if you're yappin' your gums.
准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Ready.
很好 看看能不能成功
All right. Let's see if we're drift compatible.
抓住他
Get him!
神经元负荷过度
Neural load exceeding limit.
集中精神 阿玛拉
Stay focused, Amara.
你记住 对接得越紧密 战斗力越强
Remember, the stronger your connection, the better you fight.
很简单
That's it.
阿玛拉 跳过来 快 宝贝
Amara! Come on, jump! Jump to me, baby!
必须跳 阿玛拉 跳过来 跳
You have to, Amara, come on! Jump!
阿玛拉 别纠缠过去的记忆
Amara! Don't hang on to the memory.
让它们快速闪过去 阿玛拉
Just let it flow right through you. Amara!
阿玛拉 快过去
Amara! Jump in there!
对 快 靠近点 好了吗
Yeah, come on. Get together. Ready?
一二 茄子
One, two, cheese!
拍好了
Got it.
要看吗
Want to see?
晾一会儿
Wait a sec.
阿玛拉 快让这段过去
Amara. Amara, you need to let it go.
阿玛拉
Amara!
好好听我说话
Look, just listen to my voice!
阿玛拉
Amara!
- 阿玛拉 - 爸爸 爸爸
- Amara! - Daddy! Daddy!
阿玛拉 来 跳过来
Amara! Come on, jump!
阿玛拉 我们要对接成功
Amara! We need to break the drift!
跳过来别怕
Jump to me! Come on!
我不敢
I'm scared!
宝贝 我会抓住你的 我保证 快
Baby, I will catch you, I promise. Come on!
阿玛拉
Amara!
阿玛拉 快跳过来
Amara! come on!
跳
Jump!
阿玛拉
Amara!
快摘下来
Take it off!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我在桥上
I was there.
我看见了
I felt it.
对
Yeah.
我也看见了
I felt it, too.
杰克 是我 在吗
Jake, it's me. You there?
我在
Yeah, I'm here.
快来实验室 将军要见我们
Meet me in the lab right away. Marshal wants to see us.
好 马上来
All right. I'm on my way.
你没事吧
You okay?
这是什么
What is it?
一条信息
A message.
麻子发的
From Mako.
这是她在直升机坠毁前发来的
She was trying to send it from her copter right before it went down.
是一个高密度数据包
It's a data package. High density.
复仇黑曜石发出干扰波
Obsidian Fury was jamming comms.
她是怎么发出来的
How could her signal get through?
她没成功 所以数据不完整
It didn't. At least not intact.
丢失了
So it's gone?
丢失 在数码领域是相对的
Well, "gone" is relative in the digital realm.
运用改进后的分形算法
By running a modified fractal algorithm,
我也许能重新恢复几百万字节
I might be able to reconstruct a few megabytes.
好了
There.
这是怪兽吗
Is that a Kaiju?
我在核对军防部队的怪兽档案
I'm checking against PPDC Kaiju archives.
没有匹配的结果
No match against the database.
继续找 她一定认为这个文件非常重要
Keep looking. Whatever this is, it was important to her.
我要知道原因
I want to know why.
我更想知道 操作那台不明机甲的是谁
And I want to know who was piloting that rogue Jaeger.
（邵氏工业 中国上海）
不好意思 我来晚了
Sorry I'm, uh, I…I'm late.
我以为你还在悉尼
I…I thought you were still in Sydney.
委员会已经在紧急会议上批准使用无人机甲
那太好了
That's great.
我以为你会更激动 博士
Thought you'd be a little more enthusiastic, Doc.
没有 我有点累 太好了
Yeah, no, I'm-I'm pumped. This is great.
只是这个时间点出现了袭击事件
Uh, it's just the timing of everything, with the attack and all,
总觉得
feels a little…
我就在现场 我知道发生了什么
I was there. I know what happened.
如果当时我们的无人机甲在
悉尼的悲剧 本可以避免
神经元对接程序终止
Neural connection terminated.
现在所有人都看明白了
对 确实如此
Yeah. Uh, I guess they do.
所以纵观全局 袭击并不是一件坏事
如果你换个角度来看 可以这么说
If you look at it sideways and you squint, then maybe you could say that.
请问 你这是在干什么
Uh, I'm sorry, what are you…what's going on here?
委员会要求我们四十八小时之内 完成全面部署
四十八小时…
48 is a…
这是我毕生的心血
去执行
Get it done.
好的 是
Okay. Yeah.
没有问题 我去干
Not a problem. That-That'll be fine.
四十八小时
根本不可能
觉得不可能是吗 那你就别干了
Y-You don't think there's a way? All right, well, then you're fired.
怎么样 现在行了吗
Okay? How about that?
没准运气好 你还可以升个职什么的
Or maybe you're promoted.
走着瞧吧 给我完成
I don't know. We'll see how it goes. Just get it done!
给我
Give me this.
亲爱的 我回来了
Hey, honey! I'm home!
抱歉 回来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
天那 事情实在是
God, things were…
知道吗 今天悉尼出了件大事
things were crazy today, with what happened in Sydney.
死了不少人 现场的情形很糟糕
All those people… it was, uh, not pretty.
邵老板也差点挂了 真死了就糟了
My boss almost got killed. That could've been bad.
也许吧 我猜 我也不确定
Maybe. I guess, I don't know.
其实没准她死了是件好事
That would've been great, actually,
我都快喘不上气了
that one is all over me.
我的意思是
I mean,
我在她的手下 一刻也不得消停
I can't get a break from her!
我一直在抱怨 不谈工作的事了
I'm ranting. Enough about work.
也不说她了
And enough about her,
我应该多关心你
really, I should be focused on you.
不如我们在卧室里好好亲热亲热
How about we have a little fun in the bedroom?
你今天过得好吗
How was your day?
好极了 是啊 那真是
Oh. That's great. Yeah, that's, uh,
那真让人激动
that's exciting.
你说什么
What's that?
会给我提提神吗
A little pick-me-up?
好吧
Well…
我们聊什么呢
what can I say?
我的心思你都知道了
You read my mind.
很多警察
Hundreds of police officers…
他们叫它复仇黑曜石
They're calling it Obsidian Fury.
是一个完全陌生的机甲
There's never been a rogue like this.
网上说
News feed said…
他们在纪念馆布置了十二台机甲
they were posting a dozen Jaegers at the memorial.
我死后
When I die,
希望也能有这么多机甲给我送行
I want that many to send me off.
你淘汰后 你老爸会给你
Your pop's gonna make you…
安排跟乳房打交道的工作
work with boobs when you wash out.
这种死法
Jaegers do not…
机甲是不会送行的
show up when the boob guy dies.
你爸爸的工作跟乳房有关
Wait, your dad works with boobs?
他是个整形医生
He's a plastic surgeon.
而且他的工作不只是
He doesn't just work with…
我不会被淘汰的
I'm not gonna wash out.
我会成为驾驶员
I'm gonna be a pilot.
好啊 你死了
Still. You die,
我给你寄个玩具机甲
meh, I post one Jaeger at your funeral.
或者是半个
Maybe half a Jaeger.
听说阿玛拉被找到的时候
I heard that's where they found Amara.
就是在半个机甲里
In half a Jaeger.
那是完整的机甲
It was a whole Jaeger.
只是个头不大而已
It just wasn't very big,
维多利亚
Viktoriya.
不大就是废物
Bigger is better.
闭上你的臭嘴
你刚才说什么
What did you say?
闭上你的臭嘴
我说的对吗
Am I saying that right?
对
Yep.
冷静
Guys.
我历经千辛万苦才到这儿
I worked every day of my life to be here.
而你什么都没做
You didn't do anything.
只是一个从大街上捡来的垃圾
You were just picked up off the street like garbage!
住手
Guys, come on!
知道我在哪儿学的吗
You know where I learned that?
在大街上 没教养的丫头
On the streets, you big, dumb…
战士来了
Ranger on deck!
她先动手的
She jumped me!
她不该在这里
She doesn't belong here!
我不要听
I don't care!
知道吗
You know,
我刚来的时候跟你们一样
when I first joined the Corps, I was just like you.
甚至更糟糕
Worse.
我一无是处
I was nobody.
可是今天下葬的那位女士森麻子说
But that woman we laid to rest today, Mako Mori,
她说 无论是谁
she said, "Whoever you are,
成为学员的那天起就是一家人
"the minute you enter this program, you join a family.
无论他们做了什么
"And no matter what they do,
无论他们有时候做的事多么愚蠢
no matter how stupid they may act sometimes…"
原谅他们 别放在心上
"…you forgive 'em and you move on".
你们只有开始相信这些话
So you start believing that. In here.
操作机甲的时候 你们才能信任彼此
And you'll start believing in a Jaeger.
将军在找你们
Marshal's looking for you guys.
哥特里布有新发现
Says Gottlieb found something.
这不是怪兽 而是一个地方
It isn't something. It's somewhere.
北地群岛
Severnaya Zemlya.
在西伯利亚泰梅尔半岛以北
Off Siberia's Taymyr Peninsula.
那地方有什么
What's in Zemlya?
什么也没有
Well, nothing anymore.
战争初期
A facility roughly in this location…
我曾经利用那个地方的一处设施
was used to manufacture Jaeger power…
生产过机甲的能量内核
cores earlier in the war.
但是几年前已经废弃了
But it was decommissioned years ago.
为什么麻子要告诉我们
Why would Mako be trying to tell us…
一个已经废弃已久的工厂呢
about an abandoned factory in the middle of nowhere?
请准许我们驾驶复仇流浪者
Sir, permission to take Gipsy Avenger…
去看看那里到底有什么
to see what the hell's out there.
（西伯利亚 北地群岛）
扫描中
Scanning.
看来麻子的信息有误
Looks like Mako's message was a dead end.
这是个废弃的地方
This place is abandoned.
不可能 等等
No, no, wait a second.
有些奇怪的信息
I'm getting some weird readings.
来了
Incoming!
攻击它的腿
Take out his legs!
我们得离开这儿
We got to get out of here!
等离子炮
Plasma cannon!
我们好像把它惹火了
Think we pissed him off.
很好
Good.
还记得以前的招数吗
You remember our old move?
当然
Hell yeah.
它好像受伤了
He looks hurt!
攻击它的动力内核
Go for his power core!
警告
Warning.
复仇黑曜石的驾驶员
Pilots of Obsidian Fury,
从驾驶舱里出来
get the hell out of your Conn-Pod!
那是什么东西
What the hell is that?
肯定是怪兽
It's definitely Kaiju.
它们有控制后肢的次级大脑
A secondary brain used to control the hindquarters.
它们是怎么来到我们的世界的
How'd they get into our world?
虫洞已经十年没出现了
There hasn't been a breach in ten years.
不然探测器一定会发现
Sensors would've picked it up.
我不认为有虫洞出现
I don't think there was a breach.
怪兽身上有明显的未知世界
Kaiju flesh has a distinct radioactive half-life signature.
放射性半衰期特征
Particular to the Anteverse.
这个家伙身上没有
This specimen does not.
你是说它来自我们的世界
Wait, so, you're-you're saying that it's from our universe?
基因指纹清楚的表明
The genetic fingerprints indicate distinctly…
这是地球生物改造技术的产物
terrestrial modification techniques, probably engineered…
可能是用战后遗留的怪兽肉体改造的
from Kaiju flesh left over from the war.
不是先驱干的
Precursors didn't do this.
这是人干的
Humans did.
老天 那团粘呼呼的烂肉
Oh, my God. That hunk of slimy crap…
居然能控制复仇黑曜石
was piloting Obsidian Fury?
我们应该到里面看一看
We got to get a look inside.
到里面去
Inside?
那玩意是怪兽的一部分
That thing's part Kaiju.
你们想想
Come on, guys.
如果现在不进去
When are we ever gonna get a chance…
以后就没有机会了
to see something like this again?
没有
Never.
没有才好呢
Never would be good.
你们不去就算了
You guys can stay here.
- 我自己去 - 不 阿玛拉
- I'm going. - No, Amar…
阿玛拉
Amara.
我们不该来这里
Guys, guys, we should not be in here.
整个程序都是融合过的
It's fused all the way through the system.
像是肌肉组织
Like… muscle tissue.
所以它行动才那么自如 酷
That's how it was able to move like it did. Cool.
可真酷
Yeah, cool.
还是和乳房打交道比较安全
Working with boobs is sounding better and better.
照这里
Shine your light over here.
只要抓住那个怪兽就行了
Oh, yeah, let's just go yank on the guts of the weird-ass Kaiju killbot.
这是什么
What is it?
我想这是一种
I think it's some sort of…
津海
Jinhai!
我说了别去拉它们
I told you not to yank on those.
快去叫人 快
Go get help! Go!
这下全完了
Man, we are so screwed!
这个处罚对她太严重了
This goes way past what she did.
已经决定了
The decision has been made.
剩下是你的事 就这样
Security will take it from here. We're done!
津海没事吧
Is Jinhai okay?
会留疤 但他还活着
He's got some scarring, but yeah, he'll live.
将军给他记察看处分
Marshal put him on probation.
美琳和苏雷什也一样
Meilin and Suresh, too.
再犯错 全都走人
They blink wrong, all of 'em are out.
这不怪他们
No, it's not their fault.
我拉他们去的
I talked them into it.
对不起 我跟将军争取了
I'm sorry, I tried to talk to the marshal, but…
可是你被项目开除了
you're dismissed from the program.
反正我也不属于这里
Never belonged here anyway.
你真这么想
Really?
很久以前我也说过这话
You know, I used to say the same thing a long time ago.
可我是真的不想待在这里
But I actually didn't want to be here.
现在也不想
Still don't.
那你为什么来
Why'd you sign up?
当时在打仗
We were at war.
我父亲是机甲部队长官
And my dad was leading the charge…
我想在这里 也许能更多了解他
and I thought… maybe I could see more of him.
甚至能和他对接
Maybe even drift with him.
有天晚上 我和奈特溜进了机甲库
Well, one night, me and Nate got into it.
做了太多蠢事 我都记不清了
It was over something stupid. I can't even remember what.
我钻进了老四代机里
So I climbed in an old Mark 4…
只想让他看看
just to show him…
没他 我照样能成为优秀的驾驶员
I didn't need him to be a great pilot.
确实够傻的
That's pretty dumb.
对
Yeah.
你走了多远
How far'd you get?
大概七步吧 信不信由你
About seven steps, well, take or leave.
到底是几步
How far did you get?
才两步 我就晕过去了 压力太大
About two steps, then I blacked out from the strain.
我醒来时第一眼就看到父亲
And the first thing I saw when I woke up was my dad,
站在我面前 脸拉得老长
just standing right in front of me, looking stern.
他说了什么
Wh-What'd he say?
他说我被项目开除了
He said I was out of the program.
他说我不配做机甲战士
He said I didn't deserve to be in a Jaeger.
总之 他说了很多
Look, he said a lot of things.
一年后 我父亲牺牲了
A year later, my dad was gone.
我再没机会证明他是错的
And I didn't get a chance to prove him wrong.
更重要的是
More importantly,
我证明自己的机会也没了
I didn't get a chance to prove it to myself.
你听我说
You listen to me.
不要用别人的话评价自己
Don't let what other people think of you define who you are.
你不会喜欢那样的自己
You won't like where that takes you.
明白吗
Do you understand?
把头抬起来
And keep your head up.
这种情况下
And you might just be…
应该像我这样摆一副酷脸
as good-looking as me in this type of situation.
我说真的
Seriously.
这张脸长得很完美
This face is, is set up well.
美也是一种负担
Beauty is a burden.
你会好起来的
You'll be all right.
邵氏工业
Shao Industries.
什么
What?
复仇黑曜石上有邵氏工业的技术
Obsidian Fury has tech in it made by Shao Industries.
这不可能
That's impossible.
朱尔斯和她的人
Jules and her team…
把那个机甲扫描了好几遍
scanned every centimeter of that Jaeger.
并联电缆里的绝缘超材料
Insulating metamaterials wound counterclockwise…
是逆时针缠绕的
in the shunt cabling.
只有邵氏工业也会那样做
Shao's the only company that winds them that way.
- 阿玛拉 你肯定吗 - 我肯定
- Amara, are you sure about what you're telling me right now? - Yes.
我造拳击手时 偷了很多东西
I stole a ton to make Scrapper.
我想这可能是重要的信息
I thought it might be important.
是的 谢谢
Yeah. Thank you.
邵氏工业
Shao Industries?
他们连生物部门都没有
They don't even have a bio division.
据我们所知 确实如此
Yeah, not that we know of.
电缆可能是偷的
Cabling could have been stolen,
就像阿玛拉机甲里的
just like in Amara's Jaeger.
想把黑曜石和邵氏联系起来
We're gonna need more than that…
我们需要更多的证据
to connect Fury to Shao.
问问纽特怎么样
What about Newt?
他能访问内部资料 运输单据
He'd have access to the internal records, the shipping manifests…
好 去找他
All right. Go see him.
要低调
Keep a low profile.
有任务给我
I have a mission?
总算有了
Finally.
我们去向将军汇报情况
We'll take what we know to the marshal.
（邵氏工业）
邵总 大楼一切安全
没有相关证件 任何人不许入内
我不希望部署受到任何威胁
什么情况
我会在我办公室
是
这不公平
This isn't fair.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我觉得这个处罚有点过重了
You don't deserve this.
是我犯的错
It was my fault.
我承担后果
This is on me.
阿玛拉
Amara.
下次你再造机甲时
The next Jaeger you build…
造一个大点的
make it a big one.
（圣地亚哥）
程序在线
System online.
（东京）
- 我们已经百分之百交货了 各位 - 程序在线
- And we have delivery at 100%, people. - System online.
百分之百 这才叫干得漂亮 懂吗
A hundred percent! That's the way that it's done, okay?
我跟你们说过 我们能做到
I told you we could do it,
我们做到了
and we did it!
发生故障
Malfunction.
与无人机甲375的无线通讯连接突然中断
I'm losing uplink to drone 375!
- 怎么回事 - 发生故障
- Why? - Malfunction.
怎么回事 快弄清楚怎么回事
Why? Figure out why!
我们会把知道的一切 当面告知委员会
We'll take what we know to the council in person.
准备运输机
Prep a transport.
等一下
Give me a second.
外面的无人机甲出现了故障
我们必须立即停止派遣
进入流浪者 快去
Get to Gipsy! Go!
所有驾驶员 驾驶机甲与敌方开战
All pilots, man your Jaegers and engage hostiles!
你可以的 你还好吗
Okay, you got this. You cool?
是的 超好
Yeah, super cool.
只要保持冷静
Just, uh, just stay calm.
葛斯乐博士 邵总在找你
我知道 我正要过去 我这就要
I…I know. I'm heading up! I'm heading right…
赫尔曼
Hermann.
你怎么在这儿 你怎么进来的
Uh, what are you doing here? How'd you get in here?
我有军防部队的证件
I do have PPDC credentials,
再说现在大家似乎都把心思放在
and besides, everyone else seems a little bit preoccupied…
你们老板刚刚部署的夺命无人机甲上
with the killer drones your boss just set off!
她利用了你
She used you.
没有
No.
- 她用金钱收买你 虚名诱惑你 - 没有
- She lured you with money and a fancy title. - No. No way.
在你被成功冲昏头脑的时候
And while you were basking in the glow,
她就拿走你的研究成果 为所欲为
she took your research and she twisted it.
帮我阻止她 纽特
Help me stop her, Newton.
帮我拯救世界 就像上次那样
Help me save the world like old times.
好吧 严格来说
All right, technically, uh,
上次其实是你帮我
you were helping me last time.
你就直说吧
Let's get that straight.
好
Fine.
你来帮我 其实也是帮你自己拯救世界
Help me help you save the world.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
我觉得
Well, I say, um,
我觉得 别开枪
I say… Don't shoot!
别…别 别开枪
该死 为什么我的中文讲得这么烂
Goddamn it! Why can't I get this language?
怎么回事
What's happening?!
阿玛拉 那是机甲吗
Amara! Are those Jaegers?
不 是邵氏工业的无人机甲
No, they're drones from Shao Industries.
它们要干什么
What are they doing?
我不知道 它们发疯了
I don't know. They just went crazy.
赶紧逃
Hey! Clear the deck now!
立刻回你们的宿舍
Get back to your quarters right now!
是 长官
Yes, sir!
快走 走
Go, go, go!
快跑 赶紧离开这里
Go! Get the hell out of here! Come on!
快点 跑 跑
Come on.
快点起来
Come on, come on. Get up.
不是吧 现在
Really? Now?
赫尔曼
Hermann!
帮个忙
A little help!
下次你能不能学学开枪
Next time, why don't you learn how to use a gun!
吃我一拳
Take that!
坏蛋 你们这些坏蛋
Vile, vile individual!
谢谢你 纽特
Thank you, Newton.
要不是因为我不习惯在别人面前做亲密动作
I'd hug you if I didn't have a rule about…
我真想抱抱你
public displays of affection.
行啊
It's fine.
- 没事 - 好吧
- Oh, to hell with it. - Okay. All right.
你抱够了吧
If you're done groping me,
我们快去对付无人机甲吧
let's take care of the drones, right?
（错误）
关闭所有程序 快
所有人 离开实验室
Everyone, get out of the lab…
不然我就开枪了
or I will shoot you!
我会一人给2000
I will shoot you twice!
我就知道你会发疯的
你被开除了 出去
You're officially fired. Get out.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
怎么做才能阻止它
How do we stop this?
我有后门 赫尔曼
There's a back door, Hermann.
后门在哪里
To what?
我设计的子程序
To the drone subroutine.
我在子主程序里安装了后门
I added a subroutine…
以备将来我可以随时进来看看
just in case I want to get in here and poke around down the road.
你这狡猾的混蛋
Oh, sneaky bastard.
我知道 是吧
I know, right?
（危险 错误）
（系统信息 已确认 启动虫洞协议）
你刚刚干了什么
What did you just do?
我已经计划了十年的事
What I've been planning the last ten years.
我要终结这个世界
I'm ending the world.
（美国 火奴鲁鲁）
（夏威夷 火奴鲁鲁 探测到虫洞）
（中国 香港 探测到虫洞）
（阿拉斯加 安克雷奇 探测到虫洞）
我的驾驶员都在哪儿
报告近况
多地出现裂缝
是那些无人机甲
全体驾驶员 探测到虫洞
All pilots, breaches detected.
无人机甲正在打开虫洞
Drones in the field are opening multiple breaches…
环太平洋多个地区告急
across the Pacific Rim.
为什么 你为什么要这么做
Why? Why would you do this?
我为什么要这么做
Why would I do this? Mm.
好吧
Well,
我觉得我不会这么做
I guess I wouldn't.
一般来说不会 我并不是这种人
Well, not normally, not really my style.
我不知道
Yeah, no, I don't know,
可能是恨你们
maybe I hate you all…
不把我当回事 像对待小丑一样对待我
for treating me like an insignificant little joke of a man.
也许这就是我这么做的原因 赫尔曼
Maybe that's why he did it, Hermann…
是不是
I did it.
是 你看
Uh, see.
这就对了
There you go.
这就是问题所在
There's the problem.
我最近好像完全感觉不到自己了
I'm just not feeling totally myself these days.
你
You.
（怪兽大脑标本）
是先驱
Precursors.
非常好 赫尔曼 你懂了
Very good, Hermann, you figured it out.
跟以前一样 又比别人慢半拍
And as usual, a step behind.
纽特
Newton.
你是个好人
You are a good man.
不 赫尔曼
No. Uh, Hermann.
- 你必须阻止它 - 不 反击它们没有意义
- You must stop. - No, there's no point in fighting them.
- 你必须反击 - 我没那么强 赫尔曼
- You must fight back. - I'm not strong enough, Hermann.
- 拜托 纽曼 你必须 - 我没那么强
- Please, Newton. You must! - I am not strong enough.
他没那么强
He is not strong enough!
你们都没那么强
None of you are strong enough!
我很抱歉 赫尔曼
I'm sorry, Hermann.
他们已经控制了我
They're in my head.
放开他
你休想毁了这一切
你好 老板
Oh, hey, boss.
你们在这干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
我叫你们回宿舍去的
I told you to get to quarters!
门都被封锁了
All the doors are blocked!
我们该怎么办
What do we do?!
你是怎么背着我做的
要知道你公司百分之三十八的东西都是自动化的
I mean, 38% of your company is fully automated.
所以我在这里动个手脚
It really wasn't very hard…
在那里动个手脚
to reallocate a little over here,
真没什么难的
and a little over there,
趁你不注意的时候
and slip in a little Kaiju surprise…
我就偷偷送你个小怪兽惊喜
without you noticing.
特别是你总认为…
你是这最聪明的
我很快就是了
住手 等等
Stop! Wait, wait, wait!
纽特不能控制自己
Newt's not in control of himself!
这不是他 是先驱
It isn't him! It's the Precursors.
肯定是因为他和怪兽对接的时候
They must have infected his mind…
被感染了大脑
when we drifted with the Kaiju.
你闭嘴
Shut up!
安保 抓住葛斯乐博士
他要是反抗 就地枪毙
你们待在这里
You stay here.
我们去试试接近流浪者
We're gonna try and get to Gipsy.
你准备好了吗
You ready for this?
没有 你呢
No. You?
没有 数到三就跑
No. On three.
好
Great.
一 二
One, two…
有人吗
Hello? Anyone there?
哥特里布
Gottlieb?
杰克 谢天谢地
Jake! Thank God.
我们遇到袭击了
We're under attack!
你赶紧让丽雯关掉无人机甲
You need to force Liwen to shut down the drones!
不是她 不是丽雯
It isn't her. It isn't Liwen.
是纽特
It-it was Newt.
他被先驱感染了
The Precursors, they've infected him.
它们控制了他的大脑
They're controlling his mind.
哥特里布
Gottlieb,
你能让他关掉无人机甲吗
can you get him to disable the drones?
不行 他已经跑了
No. He got away.
哥特里布 关掉它们
Gottlieb, shut 'em down.
我已经进入主程序
它是想把你锁在外面
It-It's trying to lock you out.
反馈回路
Feedback loop.
哥特里布 到底怎么回事
Gottlieb, what the hell is going on?
哥特里布
Gottlieb!
哥特里布 关掉它们
Gottlieb, shut 'em down…
不然我们就死定了
we're gonna die!
关掉它们
Shut 'em down!
（反馈手雷完成 上传）
太棒了
Yes!
（虫洞）
丽雯关掉了无人机甲
Liwen has disabled the drones.
虫洞被关上了
The breaches are closed.
重复 虫洞被关上了
I repeat, the breaches are closed.
不
Oh, no.
又怎么了
"Oh, no" what?
有三只怪兽已经爬出来了
Three Kaiju have gotten through.
分别在韩国 俄罗斯海岸和中国东海
South Korea, Russian coast, and East China Sea.
两个四代 一个五代
Two Cat 4s and a Cat 5.
收到
Copy that.
返回基地
Get back to the dome.
我们需要所有的帮助
We're gonna need all the help we can get.
姑娘们 没事吧
You girls okay?
没事 长官
Yes, ma'am!
进展如何
All right, what do we got?
仍在接收报告
The reports are still coming in,
不过无人机甲干掉了机甲
but drones took out Jaegers…
和环太平洋的机甲基地
and Shatterdomes across the Rim.
好吧 我们这里有多少机甲
All right. How many Jaegers do we have here?
可操作的 就只有复仇流浪者
Operational? Gipsy Avenger, barely.
就这个吗
That's it?
对
Yeah.
好吧 我们需要更多的机甲投入战斗
Okay. We need more Jaegers up and running…
不然很快就会被灭掉
or this is gonna be a short fight.
就算我们办得到
Even if we can,
可我们所有的驾驶员非死即重伤
all of our other pilots are either dead or severely injured.
我们一次解决一个
Okay, okay, one disaster at a time.
我们先处理机甲的问题
Let's just focus on those Jaegers.
小不点 你过来
Smallie, come over here.
你帮朱尔斯维修机甲行吗
I need you to help Jules with the repairs. Can you do that?
我以为我被开除了
I thought I was kicked out.
现在准你归队
I'm kicking you back in.
她能把破铜烂铁变成机甲
She's pretty good at turning junk into Jaegers.
没问题吧
You good with that?
太好了
Hell yeah.
我们任务很重 时间却不多
Right, we got a lot of work to do and not a lot of time.
有东西飞来了
We got incoming!
我带来了帮手
I brought some help!
白蛇 伯劳刺
Hakuja, Shrikethorn,
还有大家伙 雷怪
and the big fella, Raijin.
我随意给它们起了这些名字
I took the liberty of assigning the designations.
好吧 带刺的和傻大个
Well, the spiky guy and the big idiot…
正在离开城市 并向大海前进
are moving away from the cities and towards the ocean.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
也许它们是想在中国东海和白蛇会合
Maybe they're trying to link up with Hakuja in the East China Sea.
是的 我猜纽特知道它们想干什么
Yeah, I bet Newt would know what they're up to,
不过得先问出来
if we can get it out of him.
对 我们得先找到他
Yeah, we'd have to find him first.
有离这些怪兽更近的机甲吗
Any Jaegers closer to those Kaiju than us?
秦都和萨林克基地幸存的机甲在尽力拦截
What was left of the Chin-do and the Sakhalinsk domes tried to intercept…
注意 是尽力
emphasis on "tried."
恐怕我们得靠自己了
I'm afraid we're on our own.
肯定有什么在那
There's got to be something here.
肯定有什么东西在东海
Something in the East China Sea.
也许它们要去的不是东海
Maybe that's not where they're headed.
把怪兽在战争中移动的地图展开
Pull up a map of Kaiju movement from the war.
把数据放到主屏上
Pushing data to main display.
怎么回事 你还知道些什么
What, do you know something we don't?
你说过 我们得明白敌人的目的
You said we need to understand our enemy's objective…
才知道是否已经打败了它们
to know we've beaten them.
万一怪兽并不是
What if the Kaiju weren't…
盲目的攻击我们的城市呢
blindly attacking our cities during the war?
万一我们是正好挡路了呢
What if we were just in their way?
对 就是这里
Well, right here.
日本的富士山
Mount Fuji, Japan.
推测下白蛇 伯劳刺和雷怪的路线
Extrapolate for Hakuja, Shrikethorn and Raijin.
（富士山）
富士山 可为什么呢
Mount Fuji? But why?
为了稀有元素
Rare earth elements.
富士山是一座含有大量稀有元素的火山
Mount Fuji is a volcano rich in rare earth elements.
怪兽的血液可以与之产生剧烈的反应
Kaiju blood reacts extremely violently with rare earth elements…
我的燃料推进器试验正是以此为基础
is the basis of my fuel-thruster experiments.
不好意思
Excuse me.
听着不妙 不太妙 对吧
Oh, that sounds bad. That's bad, right?
相当糟糕
Very.
富士山是活火山
Mount Fuji's active,
是一个地质压力点
a geological pressure point.
根据怪兽血液可达到的质量比
Based on the blood-to-mass ratio of the Kaiju,
这个反应会引起喷发事件
the reaction would cause a cascade event,
点燃环太平洋的火圈
igniting the Ring of Fire around the Pacific Rim.
数十亿吨的有毒气体
Billions of tons of toxic gas…
和灰烬会喷到大气层之中
and ash will spew into the atmosphere,
灭绝地球上一切生物
wiping out all life.
然后帮先驱达成改造地球的目的
And finish terraforming the Earth for the Precursors.
不能让它们抵达富士山
We can't let 'em reach Mount Fuji.
我问问朱尔斯机甲的维修进度
I'm gonna check with Jules for Jaeger repairs.
就算我们有一百架机甲
Even if we had a hundred Jaegers,
可时间不等人
there's no way to intercept in time.
你的推进器能用吗
What about your thruster pods?
不 不行
Oh, no, no, no, no.
还没准备好
They're not, they're not ready.
不行吗
Can they be?
理论上 如果 也许
Well, in theory, if it, um… maybe,
在你的帮助下
with-with your help.
哥特里布 理论上是什么意思
Gottlieb, what does that mean, "in theory"?
就是今天能行的意思
Today… it means yes!
（手臂安装中）
军刀雅典娜 英勇保护者和凤凰游击士 可以出战
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo, and Bracer Phoenix are good to go.
这可不太够
It's not a lot to work with.
如果把黑曜石技术用在流浪者身上
If Liwen can patch some Fury tech into Gipsy,
说不定可以
that might help.
好 全力以赴做好部署工作
Okay. Prep everything we got for deployment.
好的 你要活着回来
Okay. Don't get yourself killed.
你也是
You either.
这是什么情况
Well, that's confusing.
你还是别分心了
Let's just stay focused.
我们只有四架机甲
We got four Jaegers…
而对手是两个四代和一个五代
against two Category 4s and a Five.
总比只有一架流浪者强多了
It's better than just Gipsy.
我们还需要驾驶员
We still need pilots.
我们有他们呢
We have 'em.
该死
Oh, shit.
如果我父亲在这里
If my dad was here,
他或许会高谈阔论一番
he'd probably give you a big speech.
让你们觉得战无不胜
Make you feel invincible.
我不是我父亲
I'm not my father.
我不是一个英雄 我跟他不一样
I'm not a hero like he was.
跟罗利 贝克特以及森麻子都不一样
Like Raleigh Becket and Mako Mori.
但他们也不是一开始就是英雄
But they didn't start out that way.
他们都是人 学员做起的
They started out as cadets,
跟你们一样
just like you.
我们一想起他们就觉得是巨人
We remember them as giants…
是因为他们形象高大
because they stood tall.
因为他们团结
Because they stood together.
你们的父母是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who your parents are,
背景不重要
where you came from,
人们是否相信你们也不重要
who believed in you and who didn't.
重要的是 我们现在是家人
We are a family now.
是地球最后的防御
And we are Earth's last defense.
这是属于我们的时代
This is our time,
我们有机会去改变这个世界
this is our chance to make a difference.
让我们打起精神 一起干掉他们
Now let's mount up and get it done!
听明白了没有
Do you understand?
是 长官
Yes, sir!
机甲驾驶员
Jaeger pilots,
你们明白了没有
do you understand?!
是 长官
Yes, sir!
你们明白了没有
Do you understand?!
是 长官
Yes, sir!
现在跟我一起拯救世界
Now help me save the world.
我们上吧
Let's do this.
程序在线
System online.
开始神经元对接
Initiating neural handshake.
建立神经元对接
Establishing neural link.
阿玛拉 过去
Amara, jump in there!
神经元对接很强 很稳定
Neural handshake strong and steady.
在真正的机甲里感觉如何
So…how does it feel to be in a real Jaeger?
对接感觉还不错
Bigger's not bad.
好了 全体机甲报数 可否发射
All right, all Jaegers sound off. Go-no-go for launch.
英勇保护者 可以发射
Guardian Bravo, go.
军刀雅典娜 可以发射
Saber Athena, go.
凤凰游击士 早就该发射了
Bracer Phoenix, let's go already.
收到
Copy that.
指挥中心
Command,
我们可以发射了
we are go for launch.
收到 复仇流浪者
Roger, Gipsy Avenger.
十秒后点火
Ignition in ten seconds.
九
Nine,
八
eight,
七
seven,
六
six,
五
five,
四
four,
三
three,
二
two,
一
one.
点火
Ignition!
警告 超出结构承载极限
Warning. Exceeding structural limits.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我奶奶以前经常给我放这个
My grandmother used to play it for me.
让我保持冷静
Keeps me calm.
那我怎么办
What about me?
我不冷静 哥们儿 我冷静不下来
Not calm, man, not calm.
就知道能行
I knew it would work.
（日本 东京）
（警报 怪兽来袭）
流浪者呼叫指挥中心 已找到目标
Gipsy to Command. Targets acquired.
收到 流浪者
Roger that, Gipsy.
城市里的人都在地下防空洞 他们很安全
Everyone in the city is secured in underground shelters.
你们可以执行任务了
You are clear to engage.
收到指令 等不及了
Solid copy. Going hot.
凤凰游击士跟着我 我们干掉雷怪
Bracer Phoenix, on me. We'll take Raijin.
收到 流浪者
Roger that, Gipsy.
军刀雅典娜 英勇保护者 你们干掉另外两个
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo, you take the other two…
收到
Copy that.
轮到我们来拯救世界了
It's our turn to save the world.
但愿吧
Let's hope so.
听我口令
On my mark.
三 二 一 上
Three, two, one, mark!
开火
Fire!
流浪者 雷怪的面板能吸收攻击的能量
Gipsy, Raijin's faceplates are absorbing the hits…
再反过来攻击你们
and throwing the energy back at you!
看它怎么吸收这个
Let's see it absorb this.
这家伙能扛多少栋楼啊
How many buildings can this thing take?!
伯劳刺来了
Shrikethorn inbound!
各位 我们需要支援 马上
Hey, guys, we could use a little help over here! Right now!
收到 军刀
Copy that, Saber.
维柯 干掉伯劳刺
Vik, take out Shrikethorn.
我正在干
On it.
军刀雅典娜 英勇保护者来支援了
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo coming to assist!
启动电弧鞭
Activating arc whip!
这就对了 你赶紧跑吧
Yeah, that's right! You better run!
这东西不难对付
These things ain't that tough.
凤凰游击士 注意你六点钟方向 敌方抵达
Bracer Phoenix, watch your six! Hostile inbound!
收到
Copy that!
好吧 又是巨型机器人
Okay, we're going with giant robots again.
很好 真有创意 伙计们
All right, real original, guys.
我一点都不惊讶 一点都不惊讶
I'm not impressed. I'm not impressed.
（邵氏工业）
有动静 东南方三千米 出现大量敌人
We've got movement! Multiple hostiles, three kilometers southeast.
丽雯 你在看吗
Liwen! Are you reading this?
这是我的一个自动化工厂
That's one of my automated factories.
是纽特 他在东京
It was Newt. He's in Tokyo.
我正在找出他的位置
Locating his position.
是敌方 他们正快速靠近
Hostiles, one klick away and closing fast!
全体机甲 准备行动
All Jaegers, brace for contact.
重复准备行动
Disengage and brace for contact!
好 很好
All right.
上吧 好的
Let's go, all right. Go, go, go, go!
冲 上吧 宝贝
Go, baby, go, baby!
（改变撕裂虫路线）
它们要去哪里
Where they going?
好大一只啊
Well, he's pretty big.
全体机甲前进 把所有火力都用上
All Jaegers, advance and fire everything you've got…
听我口令
on my command!
上
Go!
（军防部队保卫我们的未来）
保卫者 快退下
Guardian, stand down!
交给我们
We've got this!
马上回来 这是命令
Negative! That's an order!
这些可恶的年轻人
You freaking teenagers.
目标是眼睛
Go for the eyes!
哪一只
Which ones?
全都打
All of them.
伊利亚 苏雷什 回复
Ilya, Suresh, report.
收到没有 你们俩 回复
Do you copy? Come on, guys, sound off!
英勇保护者 报告情况
Guardian Bravo, give me a sitrep.
你们没事吧
You guys okay?
保护者倒下了
Guardian's down.
我在驾驶室出不去
I'm pinned in the Conn-Pod.
苏雷什
Suresh.
苏雷什 他没撑住
Suresh didn't make it, sir.
收到 保护者
Copy, Guardian.
待在那里别动 我们尽快派人过去帮忙
You just stay put, and we'll send you help as soon as we can.
凤凰游击士 报告
Bracer Phoenix, report.
你们没事儿吧
You guys okay?
撞坏了一点
We're a little banged up,
但还能战斗
but we're still in the fight.
我们也是 军刀
Us, too, Saber.
我是说军刀雅典娜 长官
I mean, Saber Athena, sir!
军刀 凤凰游击士 准备在下列坐标进行拦截
Saber, Bracer, prepare to intercept at the following coordinates.
- 我们来干掉它们 - 动起来 别迟了
- Let's finish this. - Move your ass, and don't be late.
收到 凤凰游击士 快点走
Copy. Bracer Phoenix hauling ass!
流浪者呼叫指挥中心
Gipsy to Command,
有敌人的战略扫描图吗
do you have a tactical scan of the hostile?
正在评估传感器连接的数据
Assessing data from their sensors.
我们拿到了 流浪者 但仍在处理
We have it, Gipsy, but it's still compiling.
没时间了 能定位大脑吗
No time. Can you locate the brains?
敌人的中央大脑有防护甲
Hostile's central brain mass is heavily armored.
你们的武器无法穿透
Your weapons won't be able to penetrate.
那次级大脑呢 这个怪物有次级大脑吗
What about a secondary brain? This son of a bitch have one of those?
这个怪兽有三个次级大脑
Hostile has three secondary brains,
每个组成部分配备一个
one for each component Kaiju.
报告正在发送
Sending intel.
军刀雅典娜 确认收到
Package confirmed for Saber Athena!
凤凰游击士收到
Confirmed for Bracer Phoenix.
好了 大家跟着我 保持警惕
All right, team, follow my lead and stay alert!
发动丽雯给我们准备的黑曜石技术吧
Fire up some of that Fury tech Liwen grabbed us?
你懂我 搭档
Read my mind, partner.
- 受损评估 - 弹出 弹出 弹出
- Damage detected. - Eject! Eject! Eject!
驾驶员 弹出
All pilots, eject!
（阿纳海姆电子公司）
阿玛拉
Amara!
警告 神经元负荷过度
Warning. Neural load exceeding limit.
奈特
Nate! Nate!
奈特 保持清醒
Nate! Stay with me! Stay with me!
站起来 奈特
Get up! Nate!
驾驶员倒下
Pilot down!
倒是站起来啊 你这一堆烂铁
Get up from that, you pile of junk!
回见
Bye!
丽雯 你能支援一下他们吗
Liwen! Is there anything you can do to help?
我需要更多的时间
I need more time!
我们没时间了
We don't have any!
如果怪兽抵达富士山
If the hostile reaches Mount Fuji…
收到指示
Understood.
它休想到山顶去
Not gonna let that happen.
杰克 没有搭档 你不能驾驶流浪者
Jake, you can't operate Gipsy without a copilot!
压力会让你神经崩裂的
The strain will tear your mind apart!
现在该怎么办
What do we do now?
去和其他人重组
Regroup with the others.
阿玛拉
Amara!
复仇流浪者
Gipsy Avenger,
我是阿玛拉·纳玛尼
this is Amara Namani!
我马上就来支援你
Stand by for assist.
阿玛拉 不要 你跳不过来
Amara, don't. You won't make it…
我能行
I'm gonna!
不要
Don't! Don't!
我跟你说了
I told you.
我什么时候听过话了
Since when do I listen?
阿玛拉 该你上了
Amara, you're up.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
给你们俩让路
Getting the hell out of your way.
交给你了 兄弟
You got this, brother.
（弹射）
弹出程序启动
Ejection sequence initiated.
弹出程序成功执行
Ejection sequence successful.
可以了吗小不点
You ready for this, smallie?
试试才知道
One way to find out.
好吧
Okay.
待命 指挥中心
Stand by, Command.
启动神经元对接
Initiating neural handshake.
神经元正在对接
Establishing neural link.
加把劲
Come on.
本想做个拉风的动作 这下可好
Yeah, that was supposed to be epic, but it wasn't.
一点也不拉风
Definitely not.
警告 级联故障 多个程序离线
Warning. Cascade failure. Multiple systems offline.
重新启动
Reboot!
好 重启中
Okay, okay, I'm on it.
呼叫流浪者
Command to Gipsy. Hostile is…
怪兽距离富士山山顶还有两公里
two kilometers from the summit of Mount Fuji…
并在快速靠近
and closing fast!
哥特里布 推进器里剩下的燃料
Gottlieb, do you have enough fuel left in your thrusters…
能把我们送到大气层吗
to launch us into the atmosphere?
大气层
The atmosphere?
对
Yeah.
应该能 但你们下来时就减不了速了
Possibly, but there won't be enough to slow your reentry…
我们不需要减速
We don't need to slow down.
我们把流浪者砸到怪兽身上
We're gonna drop Gipsy right on top of that thing.
我的逃生舱已经弹出去了
I just ejected my escape pod.
是 我们两个都用我的
Yeah. We'll have to use mine.
杰克 只有一个推进器有足够的燃料
Jake, there's only one thruster with enough fuel remaining.
把位置发给我
Sending location.
好的 查看中
All right, checking.
距离太远了
We're too far away.
这方法行不通
We're not gonna make it.
复仇流浪者 数据已经入站
Gipsy Avenger! Transport inbound!
远程程序在线 等待支援
Remote systems are online. Sending help!
拳击手
Scrapper!
我已到达推进器位置 原地等待
I've located the thruster pod! Stand by!
快点快点 步子迈大点
Come on, come on! Move them little legs!
推进器的动力太强了
The thruster's way too strong.
我们根本抓不住它
There's no way we can hold on to it!
丽雯 你有办法吗
Liwen, what do you got?
我把它焊到你们手上
I can weld it to your hand.
我升级了拳击手的武器
I upgraded Scrapper's weapons.
漂亮 我正打算那么做
Nice. I was actually gonna do that.
别吹牛
No, you wasn't.
我没吹牛
Yes, I was.
我们只有一次机会
We only got one shot at this.
是的 那就一招制胜
Yeah! Then let's make it count.
我卡住了
I'm stuck!
呆在那里
Stay there!
我们砸下时的分量能重一点
You're an extra ton we can drop on that thing!
快要解体了
She's coming apart!
马上就到了
Almost there!
我们在偏离轨道
We're drifting off course!
发射等离子炮
Use the plasma cannon!
正在解除安全协议
Disengaging safety protocol!
等离子炮已启动
Plasma cannon engaged.
警告 超出结构强度极限
Warning. Exceeding structural limits.
起作用了
It's working!
机甲结构损坏
Structural failure.
稳住
Hold on!
快点
Come on! Come on!
目标已锁定
Target locked!
杰克 阿玛拉 快启动逃生舱
Jake, Amara, you need to eject!
阿玛拉 断开连接 我能抓住你
Amara, disconnect! I will catch you!
我保证 快点
I promise! Come on!
（断开与驾驶员的连接）
抓住你了
I've got you.
流浪者呼叫指挥中心
Gipsy to Command,
我们即将启动逃生舱
we're getting the hell out of here!
逃生舱 启动失败
Escape pod failure.
不 不 不
No. No, no, no!
对不起 小个子
I'm sorry, smallie.
对不起什么
For what?
我们得拯救世界
We got to save the world.
你父亲会骄傲的
Your dad would be proud.
拳击手
Scrapper!
到这边来 快点
Get over here! Hurry up!
进来 我们得离开这里
Move! We have to go!
距离撞击二十千米 快离开那里
20 kilometers to impact. Get out of there!
快快
Go! Go!
进来了 快关门
We're in! Close the door!
抓紧
Hang on!
我已经抓紧了
I am hanging on!
再抓紧点
Hang tighter!
（死亡）
不
No! No!
你们别太得意了
Okay, you know what?
B计划 我还有B计划
Plan B. Always a plan B.
全员请注意 我是兰伯特战士
Anyone who's listening, this is Ranger Lambert.
纽特刚才被逮住了
Be advised, we just caught ourselves a Newt.
收到 那是兰伯特
Copy that. There he is.
你没事太好了兄弟
I'm glad you're still okay, man.
你也是 兄弟 我知道你能行
You, too, brother. I knew you could do it.
这个嘛
Well,
有人帮了我不少忙
I had a lot of help.
干的漂亮 战士纳马尼
Nice work, Ranger Namani.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
我第一次看到雪
Never seen snow before.
眼下有那么多抓眼球的东西
So out of all the things to notice right now,
你却只留意到了雪
you're noticing snow?
那个被我们干掉的超级怪兽就在那里躺着 我不确定…
Big, dead Kaiju is just, is right there, and I'm not sure if…
好 好吧
Okay, okay, all right.
你是准备在这个时候
Is this the part where you're gonna give me…
给我来一场又臭又长的演讲吗
one of those big, dumb speeches, 'cause…
是 大家都这么觉得
Did everyone think it was dumb…
还是你对我的演讲有成见
or is that just your opinion…
你自己对着镜子练习了多少回
Just be honest, how many times did you practice that in front of the mirror?
那是励志演讲
It was motivational.
成为你想成为的人
You can be whoever you want to be.
- 开打 - 好吧 你现在想打雪仗
- Fire! - Okay. Oh, now you want to play that?
我是天生的好手
I'm a natural at this.
不是天生的好手 因为
No, you're not a natural because…
你让着我点 我没玩过
Give me a break. I've never done this before.
中招了吧
There you go. Boom!
我们成功了
We did it!
《环太平洋2：雷霆再起》
你们以为结束了
You think this is over, huh?
以为你们拯救了蹩脚的世界
You think you've saved your crappy little world?
我们不会善罢甘休
We're gonna keep coming!
我们还会卷土重来
We are never going to stop,
迟早有一天
and sooner or later,
你们会被先驱者的铁蹄踏平
your luck is going to run out!
不 你脑子里的东西
Nah. The things in your head?
你的先驱者
The Precursors?
告诉他们 我们不怕
Tell them we're not afraid.
告诉他们下次
Tell 'em, next time,
不用再劳烦他们大驾光临
they won't need to worry about coming for us,
我们会亲自上门拜访
'cause we're gonna come for them.